(Sheldon:)...with a story about
a great female scientist.
(Sheldon:)Polish-born, French-educated...
(Sheldon:)...Madame Curie.
(Sheldon:)Co-discoverer of radioactivity...
(Sheldon:)...she was a hero of science.
Until her hair fell out...
(Sheldon:)...her vomit and stool
became filled with blood...
(Sheldon:)...and she was poisoned to death
by her own discovery.
(Sheldon:)With a little hard work...
(Sheldon:)...I see no reason
why that can't happen to any of you.
(Sheldon:)Are we done? Can we go?
(Howard:)The thing to remember is
you can go to outer space too.
Heh. I mean, look at me.
(Howard:)I went to this very school.
Those desks you're sitting in?
(Howard:)I was once superglued to one of them.
Mm-hm.
(Girl:)Did you go to the moon?